Do you think trauma changes people
トラウマって人を変えると思う？
or just reveals who they already were?
それとも元の本性が出るだけ？
Nah, it can super change you. You feel me?
いや、マジで人を変えるよ
わかるだろ？
It can super change me, change you as a person.
人としてガラッと変わるんだよ
You know what I'm saying?
わかる？
And I feel like what the world's seeing was me go through
で、世間が見てたのは
俺がトラウマを経験して
something traumatic and me change in front of them.
みんなの前で
変わっていく姿なんだよ
And then I feel like they judge me a little cruelly, but it's over now.
ちょっと残酷にジャッジされたけど
もう終わったことだし
But I think that's kind of what happened, what was going on.
まぁ、そういうことだったんだと思う
But then they'll see the headlines with the bulls**t.
でも見出しになるのは
クソみたいな話ばっか
Do you feel misunderstood
誤解されてると思う？
or do you think you've made it easy for people to misunderstand you?
それとも自分から
誤解されやすくしてる？
I think a lot of people misunderstand me
俺を誤解してる人は多いと思う
and I think a lot of people 100% understand me.
でも100%わかってくれてる人も
たくさんいるんだよ
And the people that understand me might not have as much of a voice
ただ、わかってくれてる人たちは
そんなに声が大きくないかもな
in a comment section or a headline. You know what I'm saying?
コメント欄とか見出しではさ
But I think a lot of people understand me to a certain extent.
でもある程度は
わかってくれてると思う
But the reason why the name of the album is They Just Ain't You,
アルバム名を
「They Just Ain't You」にしたのは
is I realize the way I think from the ground up
俺の根っこからの考え方が
is very different to the average person.
普通の人とは全然違うって
気づいたからなんだ